[{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678878331,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":16942,"timeElapsed":70958},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678891056,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":12724,"timeElapsed":83683},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678904349,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":13292,"timeElapsed":96976},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678916541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":12190,"timeElapsed":109167},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678934537,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":17996,"timeElapsed":127164},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678943960,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":9422,"timeElapsed":136587},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678951815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":7854,"timeElapsed":144442},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678954734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2917,"timeElapsed":147361},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678958370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":3635,"timeElapsed":150997},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678975048,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":15226,"timeElapsed":167675},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678990859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":15810,"timeElapsed":183486},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678999282,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":8421,"timeElapsed":191909},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679007772,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":8488,"timeElapsed":200398},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679020246,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":12474,"timeElapsed":212873},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679027669,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":7420,"timeElapsed":220295},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679032956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":5286,"timeElapsed":225583},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679040043,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7087,"timeElapsed":232670},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679043830,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3785,"timeElapsed":236457},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679058023,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":12775,"timeElapsed":250650},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679063944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":5920,"timeElapsed":256571},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679070815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":6870,"timeElapsed":263442},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679075101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4285,"timeElapsed":267728},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679085475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":10373,"timeElapsed":278102},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679089746,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":4269,"timeElapsed":282372},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679093114,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3368,"timeElapsed":285741},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679095899,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2784,"timeElapsed":288526},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679100886,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4986,"timeElapsed":293513},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679158127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":55889,"timeElapsed":350753},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679162580,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":4452,"timeElapsed":355207},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679169518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":6937,"timeElapsed":362145},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679177240,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":7721,"timeElapsed":369867},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679189115,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":11874,"timeElapsed":381742},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679192400,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3284,"timeElapsed":385027},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679195419,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3017,"timeElapsed":388046},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679198171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2751,"timeElapsed":390798},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679201940,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3768,"timeElapsed":394567},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679210146,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6720,"timeElapsed":402773},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679213699,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3552,"timeElapsed":406326},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679222121,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":8421,"timeElapsed":414748},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679225840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3718,"timeElapsed":418467},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679231745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":5904,"timeElapsed":424372},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679234313,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2567,"timeElapsed":426940},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679237065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":2751,"timeElapsed":429692},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679242352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5286,"timeElapsed":434979},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679245004,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2651,"timeElapsed":437631},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679267987,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":21748,"timeElapsed":460614},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679270755,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2767,"timeElapsed":463382},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679281363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":10607,"timeElapsed":473990},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679283648,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2284,"timeElapsed":476275},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679289002,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":5353,"timeElapsed":481629},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679291269,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2267,"timeElapsed":483896},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679298759,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7488,"timeElapsed":491385},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679301377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":2617,"timeElapsed":494004},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679304479,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":3102,"timeElapsed":497106},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679313919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":7939,"timeElapsed":506546},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679323826,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9906,"timeElapsed":516453},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679352262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":28435,"timeElapsed":544889},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679356432,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4169,"timeElapsed":549059},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679358484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2051,"timeElapsed":551110},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679362953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4468,"timeElapsed":555580},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679365922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2968,"timeElapsed":558549},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679369758,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3835,"timeElapsed":562385},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679372777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3018,"timeElapsed":565404},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679376162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3385,"timeElapsed":568789},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679406100,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":28819,"timeElapsed":598727},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679409253,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3151,"timeElapsed":601880},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679416895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":7571,"timeElapsed":609522},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679419430,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2534,"timeElapsed":612057},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679428336,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":8904,"timeElapsed":620963},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679430370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2034,"timeElapsed":622997},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679436675,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6303,"timeElapsed":629302},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679441245,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":4569,"timeElapsed":633872},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679446999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":5753,"timeElapsed":639626},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679450868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3868,"timeElapsed":643495},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679460441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":8438,"timeElapsed":653068},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679463093,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2651,"timeElapsed":655720},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679465245,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2151,"timeElapsed":657871},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679467213,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":1967,"timeElapsed":659840},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679473351,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":6137,"timeElapsed":665977},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679475552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2200,"timeElapsed":668179},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679477937,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2383,"timeElapsed":670564},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679481072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3134,"timeElapsed":673699},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679483157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2084,"timeElapsed":675784},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679489545,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":5286,"timeElapsed":682172},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679491446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":1900,"timeElapsed":684073},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679498451,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7004,"timeElapsed":691078},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679501453,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3001,"timeElapsed":694080},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679511393,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":9939,"timeElapsed":704020},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679513328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":1934,"timeElapsed":705955},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679521700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":8371,"timeElapsed":714327},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679523685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1984,"timeElapsed":716312},{"subjectID":"1lab7yrk7z","prolificID":"6619cb1e30cb95691a6dd425","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4c359b616fc752a2ef","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679525636,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1951,"timeElapsed":718263}]